Hi, people welcome to another one
Video here from the channel I'm Rafaella
Ballerini and today I'll show you to
You how to make a custom profile
From the Ruby gift like this one here is
In case you're not yet
Familiar with ggit and
The Rubi kit that are these two
Code versioning tools
You can check it here in my videos
Right I made a playlist actually
Explaining how the hit works and
Like that you apply in practice these
So today I'll show knowledge
For you how to leave the profile of
Hip-hop similar to mine that is from this
Way that as I 've already shown you
And I'm also going to show you some things
Additional that you can put
Because I didn't necessarily put
Everything you can put on actually gives
To put zillion things in number
Things and I'll show you guys
A few different there that I found by
Internet that are very cool Remembering
That the videos I 've been making
I 've been writing the script on Mars Down and
Rising this script in the repository of
Ruby kit that I'll leave here in the
Description So the first thing I
I'll show you guys how my
Né profile What's so cool here
That we're going to put during this
Video I have this repository here
Today I'm gonna teach you to do in this
Video has several information as follows
Thesis rubies that shows all the invitations
The stars I 've got the languages
That I use the most I put pictures
Also from the photos not images of the
Languages I use is my networks
All social and this little charge super
Cool who eats the comets beyond mine
Gif here too that I did at the beginning of the
Year I thought it was really cute and it's there then
For this video people to show the
Step by step for you I created a
Different account from my right to be able
Start from scratch and create with you
Things and don't follow me in her please go
Be the Rafa gallery and two but mine
This is Rafa's official account
Normal ballerini so here we have my
Fake profile that is used for
Crack the people here in the Rubi a kit
People already have the contributions here
That table of comics that in fact
Had in my profile has none
Because I didn't use this account and as
If I do the invitations he's gonna
Increasing the
And put that I want the
Private contributions appear too
So I'll put that what connected is and the
That that would be it's actually when
You see in my profile let in
My profile is normal Rafa ballerini you
You can see it's full of stuff he's got
A lot of contribution a lot of invitation that I
I did in a private repository that's not
Public these comments they will only enter
In this table on this Count if I leave
And here I already called because then
There will appear more thing right it seems that I
I do more here we go now
Finally do the most part
Interesting that it's really
Customize and redeem yourself here like you
You can see it written here as what the
People regime he's just a repository
With this readme file with all the
Information I want inside him and
Here it is already written as this
Repository is not how this is done
Project he's just a repository
Is a ballerini/regime race that is the
File that I wrote all these
Things then I'll get into this
Repository indeed is I here
Remembering inside my fake account and
I'm looking at my normal profile that
You can't even look I'll leave the
Link here in the description I will enter here
In this repository of mine which is that of the
Profile and cês can see that there is only look
There's only one file that folder here from
Workflows later I'll explain to you
What is but only have this file laugh
From me with all the information he already
It's showing everything here beauty so the
First thing we're gonna do is
Go on my fake profile and create that
Repository however the name will not be
Race ballerini isn't because like that
Rafa ballerini is for that account here
The name of the repository has to be the name
Of your user in the Rubi kit of your name is
Pedro will be losing his name is Gabriela
Gabriela's gonna be mean if a man
Not your user so here is Rafa
Ballerini two look only how cool that
Appears as soon as I
Hi my name in the Rubi kit it shows that
A message and the miss Secret Rafaella
Ballerini 2 Bars she flag and
Two that the repository with I just
Create and already show repository of that
That whilst we meet you get if you make
Shared Public in Sales with me to get
Style or is he saying that only
Special repository and you can
Use an Edmir for your profile
Rubi kit is Are you sure he
Will be public to be able to appear in the
Profile obviously and initialize it as
Edmir to start So look here
Down there is already it's already public right me
I'll leave him like this and I can already
Dictionary of me now that I'm gonna create
That even he had spoken already initialize
With Luiz of me they liked their English
People have it funny so I trying
Read in English here for you live
So will customize here our
Profile click on the lapis for us
Go edit this file and remind you that
This video me. MD he is
And are a point Mark Down that husfrom
He's a markup language a little
Different from HTML but it accepts HTML
Inside isn't that specifically of the hit
Ruby accepts and you can see that he already
Comes here with some things is also
Configured the looks only have one comment
Here's saying some things that you
You can put that the very one that I love you is
Talking to us does so leaving
Of course the maritude I'll put here in the
Description and also in the script that I'm
Of this video here that I'm recording is a
Mark Dalmas's guide so you get
Put titles like it's H1 H2 H3
With the 7 tags you can leave the text in
Can leave in Italics it's cool
You take a look here for you guys
To see all the possibilities that you
Can put here inside that file
So first thing here that we
Will do is take into account what
I'll have to be showing us is
A comment here but look how cool
Is to let your profile just take this
Comment right here look I am
Currently working
And as such a thing I'm currently is
Studying the salt thing that just something cool
To profile these emojis with
Some important information a lot
People do I'll even leave at the end here
Of the video also some examples of
Profiles that I will also do this and you
You can put in mine for example my
Current tava ballerini I don't have these
Emojis But if you want to put and
Leaving is a legal option remembering that
The emojis for you to catch you can if
You are using Windows press the
Windows. That he'll already give you the emojis
The states I don't know if appeared here
In the video because I'm sharing the
Window and not the screen but if not you
Have with another operating system You
You can search for this bug that Emoji
Padberg he has all the emojis you
Can use look only how cool you
Can copy and paste literally if
Copies here the Emoji and glue that you
Will be able to use then the tip remains
I will leave in the description the link too
Of that bag and let's get started
I gotta copy on what I did in mine
Original profile remembering that when the
People dictate we can also is
Go see with him and predicted himself in the room
Predicted how it's getting so look
Cool that stays right I'll actually
Put some things here
I'm working with the interesting
I'll give a Speed here found mute
Right in the video but I'll just write
Some information
And here I then put some
Information that is today work with
Front-end studying typescript
Contact me on email and such in fact
You don't even need it because it already appears
I put it there in my profile and
Pronouns I use It's also cool
Let's see Brazil as it's getting
Look it just got cute there with these
Emojis I'm gonna take this Rider out and I'm gonna use
A hello
Hello Oh my God I am Rafaella
Ballerini and two né that some already exist
There and now I'll take what's already in the
My original profile Let's open here the
Repository of this my profile that like the
People remember is the user's own name
Do it Rame né and I will open the file
Readme of the repository I will click on the
Little lapis when I click that one goes
Create a fort in my profile on your
Profile right when you click is from mine
Project but you can erase later here
There's no way people there when you click
In the little lapse you can see the code
And you can copy and paste
So come on I put it's a title
That even I hadn't done here I
I put hello I only told Dani two
Months here has a hi I only speak
Ballerini beauty that part here
Right after comes the sadive with the
Rubi stands gift that are these two
Giant images with total food
The stars I 've got the languages
With more
That's pretty cool what y'all always me
Ask how do you do it just
Copy and paste from my profile but it's not
Just that don't go there I copied here
So this div I'm gonna paste here with now
I already don't know where I'm gonna put I'm gonna
Put down there this information
Lives is and what's here doesn't have the tag
Is that we will be the clickable
Right when I click on these images he
Will you want to direct to my own
Kit profile Ruby And remembering that here
Oh, you're redirecting to Rafa
Ballerini that's not my profile right this
Fake and it won't be yours too if you
Copy you have to change here to the
Your user then I will already change here
For Rafael ballerini two or you
Can put to redirect to
Any other web site you want
And actually I think I'm gonna put
Here to redirect to my beak
Look how cool I think it's gonna be
Interesting in later I'll send in
My original by the way and soon after
Come the two image tags are the two
Images in fact but we also have
Than to realize that you look at what you're talking about
From the specters of Rafaella ballerini I
I'm not the Ballerina room just the room
Line 2 I don't have it all star
The invitation and much less languages
It's not because I haven't done anything yet in this
So we have to give
Look here at the URL I'll actually go from
Show you here that this is all
What's going on, right here's the time
Image that will be 180 m and here is the URL
That automatically makes this count of
Comics and also of the stars and tals
That you 've got eh you can see it's a
Big Ruby redimends see heaven then he
It's running there in the sky and there's some
Information that we are passing on
Own url that we can change by
Example and use name you
And leave the ballerini race otherwise will
To show up my information on your
Profile so we exchange Rafa here
Valeria for vallorini two here
Below also O have a user name you
Exchange for Rafa ballerini two here who
So let's see more that show icons
What is this show there with the
Chow-chow and built I'll take away I'll
Put fake let's see how that
Happened to then he took the
Icons that had before the total Stars
Total with me then let me show of
New né chuchu
And then look just showed here the icons is
One thing you can configure the
Dracula theme Must exist other themes
We must have Dark, for example
Sending the first image, not remembering
Preview ó appeared the theme analysis can
Then I 've been walking really cool it's
Different already And then you can put this
Theme give down here too
Probably to the Dracula theme put
This city is the one that got listed people
They have a repository with all the
Information is they are project
Truth I'll leave here in the description
But I'm gonna show you guys from here
Little also what are the settings
That you can do look at what I
I thought it was this, right, maybe you can have a
Another with that same proposal is that
I had seen before but this one that I
Use it is only in their regime
Repository has all specifications
Look how much stuff How many themes
Different that you can put look
All the properties you can
Pass there in the URL so I recommend
Take a look even here I'll leave
Also in the script of the video that is in the
Repository there also in the description and
That's it people this is the obstetric kit and
For you also have a notion for
Example here in my profile You can see
That's one more so it starts there
With counting the most foods
Stars I think he really counts
Everything you know here by ixos quest and
You see for example in my profile that I
I'm the one more original then
Also have SS more if I'm not mistaken
So more and there you go growing
As the quantity increases there
Of stars like these things but
So people this is something to increase the
Our own ego isn't because in fact
No one enters the profile of others and
Stay it's more not so it's quite silly
Who knows, it's just to make it cute
Profile even why he already starts
With the most that is already a very cool note
So cool we can
And with our obstetric kit in fact not
Nothing is showing up here because I don't
I made no comment but if you have
Invitations you will see that it will appear
And they're gonna be the next part of our beach
Rugby is profile I here that I put
Are all images of the languages that
I use it, so I'll copy it and I'll paste it there
It's also not here to lose you can
See then these are from here I have
I'll copy and paste but I'll show
For you where you can find
Because you may not necessarily
To use these same languages that
They use right I don't know exactly the
Where I picked up I don't remember being too much
Sincere but I'll pass on to you will
Website I already know that I know
Has all the languages that is the must ai
With must there with him there must aiko
Just look
And he has all the languages that you
Can pick up and you can download the svg and the
I'm going back here for my profile has
This little trace I had played here
That these 27 tags they form a
I will also put the tracer to stay
Cute
Good and that I had put after
There's information from my networks
Social look just how cool is YouTube
Instagram and Twitter disagreed 'Gmail
LinkedIn And for that then people I go
Also copy here is a div but I will
Pick up only the parts of social networks
Here to paste and I will create my own
Of me here div and close div and here
Our inside it keeps causing here in the
Temptation right and I'll paste here so there's
All tags with references for
O for my Brazil social networks
So when you see YouTube here he
Is redirecting to my channel
That here's the picture so I'll already go
Show you exactly that website
Here that shows all the images that
You can use It's no dev.to that
Here I will also leave here in the description
The link Oops is this one but I have
Very website that shows quite a lot
Look how cool you people can
Simply copy that it's where the
YouTube for example
Okay, I'll get Gmail's right here
Copy Probably the same and paste that
Is not button CRC
And changed something has this site has
Another also that I use left only
Remember What is the this chips so
These unto also have some
Pretty cool beds you can do go
Leave here in the description the repository
With all these links that's this people
You're adding that you want
Can see has WhatsApp telegram
Messenger protomeios fan what you
You want to do that the Armmanda tag
Where you want to go the link that goes
Be your WhatsApp and puts the immediate is
Gay I measured with src with the image there with the
Image link Look just as it is already
Getting
Ah with all my social networks
Here he's already broken here but this
Business sometimes a bugger knows has
Some profiles of some people that the
Size of a bugada so he doesn't stay
On the same line but sometimes he doesn't
Predicted it does not stay there in the profile is then
Takes a look at it but sometimes what
You have to change is there in that is
Rite height width also there goes only
Move there in the special HTML that is well
Quiet and last thing we have
Here in my not calm profile still has the
My gif Zinho here is so much that I
I left my gif people where's my gif
And I'm shocked Where's my gif This one
Will be let's see if that's my gif
And that was the same one who was Yoda
I remember in the old days I had
Put a Yoda GIF that's why
Back to exchange show you how I
I made my gif here is this site I believe
I be the Japanese and you can ride the
Your gif also actually you ride a
Photo and then you go in the creator of gifs and
Puts two photos and these two photos
Stayed interspersed you do different
Two images of yours and then she becomes one
GIF that's how I did my sent
There on the server of the disagreed at some
Message I copied the message link and there
Is the link of the gifc itself the tip
Below we'll put what the
Charge and the snake we are for
Making the agent uses the Rubi kit
Workflow is not the bit of Action I will not
Explain about it here in that video
Because otherwise it will extend a lot if you
Want the video explaining leaves here
In the comments and I have a post in the
Instagram
The step by step of how to create collection
But I'll show you what
It's exactly this zucchini you can
See it's a svg it's wont I copy and
I'm gonna stick here too but always
Remembering that these things you copy from
My profile they're from my profile So
The information that comes that neither
Rallies that the snake will eat from mine
Original profile is not the one I'm
Gluing but not just like changing here
For Ballerina race and two has one thing
That you have to do on key day
Actions so he can stay
Recharging every time you make a
New invitation right What if we do
Here the preview for giving the right profile
Here he'll just break my
Snake Animation why why is he
Directly linked there with the hit Rehab
It's question I don't have I didn't do
Here in mine as I spoke I'll leave
Down here in the description the link of the
My Instagram post I teach
Step by step making the snake and I will
To do here quickly not to get one
Very extensive video and
And there
Already carried so now let's go in mine
Profile let's see if he was ever look
Still having a kidney problem right that one
Mess I promised some configuration that I
I still haven't tidy up doesn't let me see here
The flower bow I 've already worked out that the
Rafa ballerini two né so let's see
I made Genghis and took a look only here
Two invitations, né Neuza Look just goes
Day that's different right I made an invitation
Yesterday and now today that gave me midnight
Our old man was gave time that spent
Midnight there are two days there that I
I made Comet in this profile look how cool
I hope you liked it, I'll propose
For you guys to play down here
Comments the Rubi kit of you and the
People take a look at everyone who goes
Coming up you look at the profile and go
Gives
What do you think is cool and then we go
Do in the middle that one don't know I believe
Here that in the YouTube comments they
Always put closer who are
Most liked is no longer liked So the
People will do in the middle of the stack
Overflow profiles for personal power
Accompany and be inspired too if you
Feel free to put yours here
That's it people hope they enjoyed
Of today's video do not forget to
Subscribe to the channel that I always have
Posted video Every 15 days Maybe right
It's no longer every week 'cause I'm fine
Race also follows me on the other networks
Social that I 've got I'm gonna leave
Here in the description a kiss for you
Thanks for watching the video until